Finding Aid for the Livingston Gearhart Collection of Scores, 1930-1996
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Arrangements, transcriptions, and editions of works by other named composers, 1930-2009, II; Folder 115-228
  - Ravel, Maurice, 1875-1937. Tombeau de Couperin. Menuet; arranged Menuet: [from] T. de Couperin [between 1960 and 1970], 1 ms. score (17 p.); 34 cm. + 18 parts; 32 cm.; Originally for piano; arranged for orchestra. Title from score cover. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph score (Pencil); Holograph parts (Ink, pencil). Accompanied by [4] p. of performances notes from Livingston Gearhart; 1 note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 11, Folder 205)
  - Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908. Skazka o tsare Saltane. Nu, teper, moi shmel; arranged Flight of the bumblebee 1949, 2 scores (10 p. each); 31 cm.; Cover title. East Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 11, Folder 206)
  - Romberg, Sigmund, 1887-1951. Impromptu, piano, E♭ major; arranged Impromptu in E♭ [between 1930 and 1950], 1 ms. score ([20] p.); 35 cm.; Originally for solo piano; arranged for piano 4 hands. Cover title. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 11, Folder 207)
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Quartets, strings, D. 703, C minor. Andante; arranged Unfinished stg. qt. 1990, 1 ms. score (4 leaves); 30 x 38 cm.; Caption title. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 photocopied score (4 leaves) with changes made by the Oregon String Quartet; 1 photocopied score of Schubert's original fragment (3 leaves). (Box 11, Folder 208)
  - Sgambati, Giovanni, 1841-1914. Pièces lyriques. Ländler; arranged Ländler [between 1976 and 1996], [2] p. of ms. music; 32 cm.; For piano. Title from colophon. According to a note from Pamela Gearhart, Livingston Gearhart transcribed this piece from his memory. Holograph (Photocopy). Accompanied by 1 photocopied note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 11, Folder 209)
  - Singer, Louis C., 1912-1966. What makes a good American; arranged What makes a good American?: for mixed voices (SATB) 1955, 1 score (9 p.); 27 cm.; For SATB chorus with piano accompaniment. Cover title. Includes tone syllables to be used as a choral enunciation aid. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 11, Folder 210)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Feu d'artifice; arranged Feuerwerk [between 1930 and 1950], 1 ms. score ([12] p.) + 1 ms. part ([2] p.); 33 cm.; Originally for orchestra; arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Caption title from score. Part for Piano 2 only. Both score and part are unfinished. Holograph score (Pencil); Holograph part (Ink). Accompanied by 1 score (only first page completed); 33 cm; 1 photocopied note from Livingston Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 11, Folder 211)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Pastorale, soprano, piano; arranged Pastorale [1936], 2 ms. scores; 32-35 cm.; Cover title. Holograph (Pencil) (Ink). Accompanied by 1 index card (1 leaf) presumably from Livingston Gearhart. (Box 11, Folder 212)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Petrushka. Russkii tanets; arranged Dance Russe 1935, 4 ms. parts; 35 cm.; Originally for orchestra; arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Title from Piano 2 cover. Parts include 1 Piano 1 part with corrections; 2 final Piano 1 parts; 1 final Piano 2 part. Holograph (Pencil) (Ink). Accompanied by [2] p. of ms. sketches; 36 cm; 1 index card from Livingston and Pamela Gearhart. (Box 11, Folder 213)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Pulcinella. Overture; arranged Scherzo à la Russe [i.e. Overture from Pulcinella] [between 1930 and 1950?], 1 ms. score ([1] leaf); 32 cm.; Originally for orchestra; arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Title from accompanying index card from Pamela Gearhart. Arrangement consists of opening 4 measures only. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 index card from Livingston Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 11, Folder 214)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Zhar-ptitsa. Khorovod tsareven; arranged Khorovode: from Fire bird [between 1950 and 1970], 1 ms. score ([15] p.); 35 cm. + 18 ms. parts; 31-36 cm.; Cover title from score. "Livingston Gearhart 1996"--Copyright stamp on every page. Holograph score (Pencil); Holograph parts (Ink). Emendations to score marked in blue pencil; conductor's performance markings in red pencil. Accompanied by 1 sketch from Livingston Gearhart (1 leaf); 1 note from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 11, Folder 215)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Zhar-ptitsa. Kolybelnaia; arranged Berceuse: from Fire bird 1935, 2 ms. parts; 35 cm.; Originally for orchestra; arranged for 2 pianos, 4 hands. Cover title from Piano 1 part. Holograph parts (Pencil). Accompanied by [2] p. of ms. sketches. (Box 11, Folder 216)
  - Stravinsky, Igor, 1882-1971. Zhar-ptitsa. Poganyi plias Kashcheeva tsarstva; arranged Infernal dance of Kastchei: from The fire bird [between 1930 and 1940], 1 folder.; Originally for orchestra; arranged for 3 pianos, 6 hands. Cover title from Piano 1 part. Parts for Pianos 1 and 2 only. Includes 3 ms. parts of an earlier version of the arrangement. The third piano part is present in this earlier version only. Holograph parts (Pencil). Accompanied by 2 index cards (1 leaf each). (Box 11, Folder 217)
  - Templeton, Alec, 1910-1963. Alleluia, sing nöel! 1971, 1 score (7 p.); 27 cm.; "For S.A.T.B. voices and piano or organ with optional hand bells." Caption title. Duration: ca. 2:00. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: H. Flammer (Box 11, Folder 218)
  - Travis, Merle Sixteen tons; arranged Sixteen tons: TTBB [between 1955 and 1965], 1 ms. score ([11] leaves); 32 cm.; Alternate title: First line of text: Some people say a man is made out o' mud. For TTBB chorus with piano accompaniment. Caption title. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 index card from Pamela Gearhart (1 leaf). (Box 12, Folder 219)
  - Vivaldi, Antonio, 1678-1741. Concerto ripieno, RV 152. Allegro molto Allegro molto from Concerto ripieno: RV 152 [between 1935 and 1940], 1 ms. score (p. 31-37); 34 cm.; Realized continuo for keyboard instrument by Livingston Gearhart. Caption title. Holograph (Ink); completed in pencil. (Box 12, Folder 220)
  - Warren, George William, 1828-1902. National hymn tune; arranged God of our fathers: band accompaniment for the Fred Waring choral arrangements 1951, 1 condensed score (14 p.) + 48 parts; 31 cm.; Cover title. East Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 12, Folder 221)
  - Warren, George William, 1828-1902. National hymn tune; arranged God of our fathers: organ accompaniment for the Fred Waring choral arrangement 1949, [4] p. of music; 31 cm.; Part for organ only, no song text included. Caption title. East Stroudsburg, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 12, Folder 222)
  - Warren, George William, 1828-1902. National hymn tune; arranged God of our fathers: (S.A.T.B. with three trumpets, percussion, four-hand piano and organ accompaniment) 1949, 1 score (19 p.); 27 cm.; Caption title. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee (Box 12, Folder 223)
  - Warren, George William, 1828-1902. National hymn tune; arranged God of our fathers: T.T.B.B. with soprano descant, four-hand piano and organ accompaniment 1950, 1 score (19 p.); 27 cm.; Accompaniment for trumpets, percussion, four-hand piano, and organ. Caption title. Includes tone syllables to be used as a choral enunciation aid. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 12, Folder 224)
  - Weismantel, Fred Well, anyway; arranged Well, anyway 1958, 1 score (8 p.); 27 cm.; Alternate title: First line of text: There were eight young men took a solemn oath one day. Arranged for chorus (SATB) with piano accompaniment. No location stated: Republic Music; Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Sole selling agent for this arrangement, Shawnee Press (Box 12, Folder 225)
  - Whitney, Joan, 1914-1990. Far away places; arranged Far away places: SATB with piano accompaniment 1958, 1 score (10 p.); 28 cm.; Caption title. Includes tone syllables to be used as a choral enunciation aid. Duration: ca. 4:00. No location stated: Laurel Music; Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Sole selling agent, Shawnee Press (Box 12, Folder 226)
  - Winner, Septimus, 1827-1902. Listen to the mockingbird; arranged Listen to the mockingbird [between 1940 and 1960], 1 ms. score (5 leaves); 32 cm.; Alternate title: First line of text: I'm dreaming now of Hallie. For SATB chorus with piano accompaniment. Caption title. Original tune by Richard Milburn. Holograph (Pencil). (Box 12, Folder 227)
  - Wolf-Ferrari, Ermanno, 1876-1948. Segreto di Susanna. Ouverture; arranged Secret of Suzanne [between 1930 and 1935], 3 ms. parts; 34 cm.; Alternate title: Caption title on Piano 2 part: Susanna's secret. Originally for orchestra; arranged for 3 pianos, 6 hands. Caption title from Piano 3 part. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by 1 typescript index card from Livingston Gearhart (1 leaf); 1 photocopied concert program (1 leaf). (Box 12, Folder 228)
- Compilations and sketchbooks, 1935-2004, III; Folder 229-427
  Arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Gearhart, Livingston 1940's California: sketchbook [between 1937 and 1945], 1 ms. sketchbook ([59] p.); 32 cm.; Title from accompanying leaf. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by [1] leaf from Pamela Gearhart with title; 2 ms. scores presumably with revisions; [1] leaf from Pamela Gearhart indicating dedication to Alexander Schneider; 1 ms. revised score ([6] p.) of Prelude which later became Short suite with 1 additional leaf from Pamela Gearhart. (Box 12, Folder 229)
    Contents: Lament: woodwind quintet (Gargenville 1937) -- Motet: woodwind quintet ("Revision for woodwinds, Mills College, 1941") -- Mésures sur la France ("for André Maurois, Mills, July 26, 42") -- Dialogue for 2 oboes (Aug. 42) -- Kitsch: 2 flutes (Aug. 42) -- Untitled: 2 oboes (Aug. 42) -- Dance for 2 flutes (Sept. 42) -- Epitaph (I): flute (Orinda Sept. 42) -- Prelude (1): cello and piano (Wilsonia Sept.42) -- Revision of Prelude, for string orchestra, is filed loose in the same envelope. Revision titled Short Suite (see note included) -- Grave: viola, accompaniment (Orinda Sept. 42) -- Lament: 3 oboes (Orinda Sept. 42) -- Fanfare: 3 oboes (Sept. 42) -- Invention: 2 oboes (Denver, Nov. 1942) -- Soliloquoy: oboe alone (May 43) -- Song without words II (Now I lay me down to sleep): for English horn, 2 clarinets, 2 bassoons ("for N.B.") (1941) -- Madrigal: 2 oboes (Mar. 26, 43) -- Forlana: oboe (Apr. 3, 43) -- Sonata: 2 oboes (Orinda Sept. 42) -- Canon al novescio (sp. rovescio?) ("a canonic problem"): 2 unidentified instruments (Denver, Nov. 1942) -- "Reminiscence of Ravel in 2nd phrase and last": 2 unidentified instruments (So. Orange Dec. 42) -- "A problem in form": 2 unidentified instruments (N.Y. Apr. 9, 44) -- Fragment: 2 oboes -- Song without words (I): 2 clarinets, horn or bassoon, bassoon (July 3, 1944) -- Orientale: violin and harpsichord ("for A.S.") ("6/30/44 II; piece for Merce Cunningham 1/6/45 III") (see note about dedication to Alexander Schneider) -- Child's piece: 2 unidentified instruments (1/12/45) -- Russian dance: 4 trumpets ("dedicated to Igor Stravinsky") (½8/45).
  - Gearhart, Livingston 2 piano arrangements [between 1940 and 1954], 1 ms. sketchbook ([65] p.); 32 cm.; Alternate title: American sketch. Alternate title: Baby boogie. "Waring -- 2 piano days -- [19]40-[19]54. Some of these [arrangements] subsequently published -- all are recorded commercially"--Accompanying leaf. Title from prefatory page. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by [1] leaf from Pamela Gearhart. (Box 12, Folder 230)
    Contents: [Flight of the bumblebee / Rimsky-Korsakov -- March from The love of three oranges] / Prokofieff -- American sketch: [unfinished] -- [Viennese clock: from Háry János] / Kodaly -- In dir ist Freude / [Johann Sebastian Bach] -- Baby boogie -- Star spangled banner -- [My country 'tis of thee -- La Marseillaise -- Untitled].
  - Bass clef sessions: informal music-making for fun, for two, three and four [sign for bass clef] instruments unaccompanied 1954, 1 score (55 p.); 32 cm.; Includes index. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 12, Folder 231)
    Contents: For two players. Air for two viols / Francois Couperin. Andante from Sonata (Köchel No. 292) / Mozart. Arkansas traveler. Chinese lullaby. Fugue un A B-A-D E-G-G / Egon Toast. Gavotte / Dumont. Good King Wenceslas. Habanera / Pierre Vivant. Hare and tortoise / Aesop. Hark, the herald angels sing / Mendelssohn. In the cool cellar. Jazz on rye / Chateau. MinueteuniM / Al. Rovescio. "Mixed metre" / Mozart. Passacaglia / Raimondi. Phantasm / Prokofieff. Preludelerp / J.S. Bach. Rondo from Sonata (Köchel No. 292) / Mozart. Sarabande. Sicilienne. Sinfonia / Webbe. Song of the vulgar boatman / Deranged. We three kings of Orient are / Hopkins -- For three players. Andante from Sonata, op. 26 / Beethoven. Fanfare for the hunt / Pierre Vivant. Fanfare for a procession / Claude Debussy. Gagliarda / Kuhnau. Good King Wenceslas. Hark, the herald angels sing / Mendelssohn. Little brown jug / W.H. Madrigal / Palestrina. March / Handel. Marche from "The love for three oranges" / Prokofieff. Marche Funebre / Chopin. Nocturne from "A midsummer night's dream" / Mendelssohn. Northern song / Schumann. Now the day is over / Barnby. Round on the name B-A-C-H / Beethoven. Sweet and low / Barnby. Three rounds for three. Presto / Haydn. Lacrimosa / Schubert. Roundhouse blues / Devinez. Under this stone lies Gabriel John / Purcell. Waltz Glissando. We three kings of Orient are / Hopkins. Wild horsemen / Schumann -- For four players. Auld lang syne. Base, vile blues / Devinez. Elegie / Massenet. Equali No. 1 / Beethoven. Etude / Schumann. Fanfare for a procession / Claude Debussy. Hunting song / Brahms. In memoriam / Schubert. Misspelled music. Now thank we all our God / harm. J.S. Bach. Now the day is over / Barnby. O sacred head, now wounded / harm. J.S. Bach. Prayer / Cesar Franck. Ricercare / Gabriele Fattorini. Riffin' a round. Round for four / Brahms.
  - Belles and beaus: 3- or 4-part songs for teen-age choral groups (S.A. & boys) 1957, 1 score (96 p.); 27 cm.; On cover: The Fred Waring Music Workshop. 33 selections for teenage choruses, including patriotic songs, songs for holidays, fun and folk songs, spirituals, and general songs. Delaware Water Gap., Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 12, Folder 232)
    Contents: Years of peace -- Erie Canal -- The band played on -- Loch Lomond -- O Peter, go ring them bells -- Summer reverie -- O no, John -- La cucaracha -- Where are y' goin', my pretty miss? -- Sometimes I feel like a motherless child -- Rodeo Joe -- Evensong -- Sing, all creation -- Love may go hang -- Lord of the earth -- The ghost's high noon -- Thanksgiving song -- O holy night -- Deck the hall -- Fum, fum, fum! -- Once on a lonely hill -- When Christmas morn is dawning -- Bring a torch, Jeannette, Isabella -- O Lord of beauty -- Red river valley -- Dry bones -- Who is Sylvia? -- Kentucky babe -- Cape Cod chantey -- I'm a-rollin' -- An American is a very lucky man -- Auld lang syne -- Sing your way home.
  - Choral sentences for the worship service: introits and calls to worship, prayer invitations and responses, offertory sentences, benedictions, sentences for special services, for all seasons of the church year 1966, 1 v. (unpaged); 27 cm.; For all voicings: S.A.T.B., S.A.B., S.S.A., S.A., T.T.B.B., T.B., Unison. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press Words in English. (Box 13, Folder 233)
    Contents: Glory be to God / Shipp -- Draw nigh to God / Hutson -- The Lord is in his holy temple / Hoggard -- The Lord is in his holy temple; Open now thy gates / Zaninelli -- The hour cometh / Hutson -- Enter we now the holy gate -- The Lord is in his holy temple / Cunkle -- In thy temple, Lord / Zaninelli -- Let all mortal flesh -- This is the day / Hutson -- Christ is risen / Hornibrook -- The Lord is maker of the seasons; The Lord is risen; Rejoice! / Gearhart -- Christ is born today; Christ is ris'n today / Bedford -- Alleluia!; Repent ye!; Today on earth / Gearhart -- Our King and Saviour / Hutson -- O praise the word -- Jesus stand among us / Zaninelli -- Unto us a boy is born -- Now glad of heart -- Let Christians all rejoice -- He is risen / Hutson -- Be still and know / McCormick -- Hear our prayer, O Lord: with descant / Hoggard -- Let the words of my mouth / Bright -- Day by day / Powell -- Cleanse the thoughts of our hearts / Van Velsen -- May the words of my mouth / Frackenpohl -- Hear thou, most gracious Lord / Hutson -- To my humble supplication / Sektberg -- Dear Father, hear our prayer; Be still and know / Cunkle -- Hear our prayer, O Lord / Hutson -- Hear our prayer, O Lord; Let the words of my mouth / Gearhart -- Almighty Father, hear our prayer / Hutson -- All things come of Thee / Gearhart -- Almighty God, thou giver / Rider -- Honor the Lord / Gearhart -- Bless thou the Gifts; Almighty Father, bless the word / Hutson -- Let me understand / Roff -- Thy word is a lantern; Teach me, O Lord / Hutson -- God be in my head / Powell -- Bless us, Lord / Bedford -- May the grace of God go now with us / Bright -- May the star of Bethlehem guide you / Banyard -- Baptism sentences -- Communion sentences.
  - A Christmas singing bee: two-part songs for treble voices (S.A.) with descants and optional divisi: a Christmas supplement to A singing bee [1962], 1 score (48 p.); 27 cm.; On cover: The Fred Waring Music Workshop. With piano accompaniment. Delaware Water Gap, Pennsylvania: Shawnee Press (Box 13, Folder 234)
    Contents: The wise may bring their learning -- We'll dress the house -- The cherry tree carol -- On Christmas Day in the morning -- Born today is the Child Divine -- Carol of the wind -- O come, all ye children -- Dear Santa, have you had the measles -- God rest ye merry gentlemen -- Sleep, holy Babe -- Rise up, shepherds -- A jingle-bell travelogue -- O come, poor folk and lowly -- Some children see Him -- How far is it to Bethlehem? -- It came upon a midnight clear -- The selfish carol -- The three scrooges -- Christmas comes 'round -- O holy night -- O little town of Bethlehem -- Behold a tender newborn babe -- Hark! The herald angels sing.
  - Clarinet sessions: informal music-making for fun, for two, three and four clarinets, unaccompanied 1948, 1 score (43 p.); 32 cm.; "For intermediate and advanced players; a variety of styles from Palestrina to jazz; unusual music, interestingly arranged." Delaware Water Gap, Penna.: Shawnee Press (Box 13, Folder 235)
    Contents: For two players. Adeste fideles; Allegro / Mozart; Auld lang syne; Calisthenic canon / Klengel; Canon / Alec Wilder; Contrariwise duet / André; Dance / Corelli; Duet / C.P.E. Bach; Duet / after Mozart; Duettino / C.P.E. Bach; God rest ye merry, gentlemen; Motet / Asola; Northern song / Schumann; O, my heart, it is so sore / Henry VIII; PreludulerP / J.S. Bach; Procession / Rousseau -- For three. Adagio; Allegro / Mozart; Auld lang syne; Barbara Allen: English folk song; Canon / Alec Wilder; Dance / Corelli; Gearshift canon / Dr. Cooke; God rest ye merry, gentlemen; Hash for three / Mr. Zilch; Iste confessor / anon., 14th century; Lament (round) / Brahms; Madrigal / Palestrina; Northern song / Schumann; Now is the month of maying / Morley; O, my heart, it is so sore / Henry VIII; Round for three / Hilton; Song / Benjamin Franklin; Three rounds. Under this stone lies Gabriel John / Purcell; The greenwood tree / anonymous; Three blind cats: a jazz round / Suomynona; Trio / Beethoven; Tune from "Peter and the wolf" / Prokofieff; Variations on "London Bridge" in five styles. Sarabande from the "Royal bridge music" / nach Handel; Allegretto from "Suspension symphony" / nach Haydn; Mazurka (abridged version) / à la Chopin; Ce qu'on a vu au dessus le pont / à la Debussy; High bridge / as per "Stuff" Smith; Wintertime / Schumann -- For four. Adeste fideles; Canon / Alec Wilder; Drink to me only with thine eyes; EXchange 3456: jazz study; Londonderry air; Minuet / Haydn; Pastorale / Stravinsky; Perpetual motion / Tschaikowsky; Prayer: from "Hansel and Gretel" / Humperdinck; Quartet / Haydn; Ricercare / Fattorini; Sweet and low / Barnby; Swing! (low, sweet chariot); Turkey in the straw; Wintertime / Schumann -- Solo. Presto / Frederick the Great.
  - Gearhart, Livingston Collected material 1944 1944, 1 ms. sketchbook ([93] p.); 33 cm.; Chiefly arrangements published in Livingston Gearhart's Sessions series. Some folk songs copied from other sources cited in sketchbook. Cover title. Holograph (Pencil). Accompanied by [Untitled work for 2 horns] / Mozart ([1] leaf); Air / Old English and Air / Purcell [for two unspecified treble instruments] ([1] leaf). (Box 13, Folder 236)
    Contents: March of the musketeers of the King of France: d'apres Rousseau: hautbois -- Etude for one, or Canon for 2 violins / Mendelssohn -- [Untitled piece] / Josquin -- Welsh morris dance -- [Untitled piece] / Pierre de la Rue -- Lady Nelson's Reel -- Al rovescio: minuet from Violin sonata / Haydn -- St. Patrick's day -- Schöne minke -- Schottische -- Canon cancrizans: a tre / Haydn -- Preluduler P: canon recte e retro [in] G minor for oboes-sax: from The musical offering / J.S. Bach -- Madrigal / Purcell -- [The alphaset?] / Mozart -- Round: Turn amarillis / Hilton -- Fanfare, op. 44, no. 2 / Brahms -- Now is the month of Maying: in C major, written for cl. + trumpet / Morley -- Round / Purcell -- Canon on B-A-C-H-: for 2-piano-fun / Beethoven -- Madrigals / Asola -- Nurse's tale: key for oboe-sax: Staccato study / Tschaikowsky -- March of the tin soldiers: 3 sax arranged; Hobby horse: picc + 3 fl.: Triple tongue study; 4 cl. B♭ / Tschaikowsky -- Russian folk song after Tchaikowsky: 3 sax (oboes) -- Canons / Beethoven -- Epitaph / Benjamin Cooke -- [Untitled piece] -- Ancient Roman melody (According to Burney) -- Chant des syrenes -- Ricercare, 4 cl. / Gabriel Fatorini -- Folk songs via Bantock: O willow, willow; The vicar of Bray; My ain kind dearie, oh; O logie O'Buchan; The minstrel bay; Hunting the hare; The ash grove; Sur le pont d'Avignon; Troubadors / Chatelain de Coucy; Troubadors / Count Thibaut of Champagne, King of Navarre; Minnesingers: Summertime; In the cool cellar; Wooing; Tyrolese are happy; On the alma; [Untitled] / Liszt; O, come to me; May song; Bravely sail my bark; Wermeland; In the shade of the Garden; The old pear tree; Little cottage; Rune song; [Untitled]: Serbia; The sun hangs high; Jasmin flowe[r]; Barbara allen -- Round in 3 parts -- Chanteys (from Sharp): Oh, Johnny come to Hilo; Haul away, Joe; Sally Brown; Magnificat; Alleluia; Hymn to Apollo -- [Untitled] discant from the 11th century -- Et in terra pax hominibus bonae voluntatis / Guglielmo Dufay -- Henricus Octavus: motet / (Hawkins) -- The miracle: fragment: choral-prelude / Humperdinck -- Canon: for trumpets / Haydn -- Domine deus: Syncopes / Lassus -- Fragment: Pelleas + Melisande / [Debussy] -- Iste confessor -- [Short fragment: from the] Matthäus Passion -- Canon / Martini -- Fanfare: [Brandenburg concerto no. 1, first movement] / J.S. Bach -- Oh my heart it is so sore / Henry VIII -- Lift thine eyes: [from] Elijah / Mendelssohn -- See, the conquering hero comes: [from] Judas Macccabeus / Handel -- Fuga für das Laufwerk: tn? sax / Haydn -- The peoples [sic] joy + happy dances: from Biblical sonata / Kuhnau -- Sally Gordon: fiddle tune -- Chanson Maçonne par le Frère Americain -- Kind Jenny / Dr. Blow -- A catch / Purcell -- A Yorkshire epitaph on [the tune of?] Abbey Lubbers / Blow -- A catch / Purcell -- A rebus upon Mr. Anthony Hall, who keeps the Maremaid tavern in Oxford + plays his part very well on the violin / set by Purcell -- A catch: Silver swan -- Come follow me: Round for 3 voc / Hilton -- Mr. speaker: catch for 3 voc -- Hunting the hare: Welsh folk song –